hey guys let's solve for x we have x +
theun x + thek x plus the X going on
forever equal 441 so what value of x
would make this true step number one
let's subtract X from both sides on the
left hand side these two x's cancel so
we just have the square root of all this
stuff it's going to be equal to 441 - x
now this inside of the square root it is
also going to keep going on forever that
means that this stuff inside the square
root is the same thing as this stuff
right here this is equal to 441 that
means this right here is also equal to
441 and then the < TK of 441 is 21 let's
add X to both sides which will give us
21 + x = 441 and then let's subtract 21
from both sides and then we get X is
equal to and 441 - 21 is 420 and that is
the answer to our question that we can
put a box around it so next time you see
420 +un of 420+ of 420 going on forever
you'll be able to say that is exactly
441 how exciting